<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rights And Resources</string>
    <string name="title_activity_3">Activity3</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_rights_and_resources">Welcome to Rights and Resources</string>
    <string name="abuse">Abuse</string>
    <string name="immigration">Immigration</string>
    <string name="lgbtq">LGBTQ+</string>
    <string name="mental_health">Mental Health</string>
    <string name="police">Police</string>
    <string name="mental_health_resources">Mental Health Resources</string>
    <string name="get_help">Get Help</string>
    <string name="help_a_friend">Help A Friend</string>
    <string name="mental_help">Mental Health</string>
    <string name="immig">Immigration</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="rights">Rights</string>
    <string name="helpfriend">How can you help someone struggling with a mental illness? Listen, show your support, ask what you can do to help, and educate yourself: Listen- If your friend talks about their mental health diagnosis, don’t change the subject. Resist the temptation to give advice or dismiss their concerns. If your friend discloses personal information, keep his/her trust by not sharing the information with others. The exception is talk about suicide. When suicide is mentioned, it’s time to tell a professional and get help! If you’re feeling overwhelmed by what he/she has told you, contacting NAMI (National Alliance on Mental Illness) or another helpline can be a good way to get advice while still keeping information confidential. Show your Support- Many people with mental health disorders tend to withdraw from family and friends. Continue to invite your friend to go to dinner, study, talk, or just hang out. Even if he/she doesn’t always feel like talking or spending time together, it can be a comfort just to know that he/she has friends that care. Ask what you can do to help You can leave this open-ended (“I want to know how I can best support you.”) or suggest specific tasks that might be helpful (“Can I drive you to your appointment?”). If you know that your friend is struggling in school, it can be helpful just to offer to study with him/her. Educate yourself: Learn how to become a better ally! Discourage person from using alcohol or drugs to relieve themselves. If you’re worried about someone\'s safety please call 911</string>
    <string name="ab">Abuse</string>
    <string name="r1">Resources</string>
    <string name="r2">Rights</string>
    <string name="police_encounters">Police Encounters</string>
    <string name="r3">Resources</string>
    <string name="r4">Rights</string>
    <string name="situations">Situations</string>
    <string name="sexual_assault">Sexual Assault</string>
    <string name="resourc">Resources</string>
    <string name="laws">Laws</string>
    <string name="reporting">Reporting</string>
    <string name="tips_to_avoid_assault">Tips to Avoid Assault</string>
</resources>
